<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_US"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_US" /><updated>2020-03-19T16:56:09-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Query</title><subtitle>Bite-sized interviews for makers, indie hackers, and entrepreneurs.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><entry><title type="html">Philip Manavopoulos from Doorbell</title><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/philip-manavopoulos-from-doorbell/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Philip Manavopoulos from Doorbell" /><published>2018-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/philip-manavopoulos-from-doorbell</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/philip-manavopoulos-from-doorbell/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/manavo?lang=en&quot;&gt;Philip Manavopoulos&lt;/a&gt; is the founder of &lt;a href=&quot;https://doorbell.io/&quot;&gt;Doorbell.io&lt;/a&gt;, a tool for easily gathering in-app user feedback on all major platforms (web, iOS, and Android). Philip is from the United Kingdom, and has represented his country in sport competitions and played violin for almost 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;youve-had-some-success-using-quora-for-marketing-can-you-describe-how-youve-used-it&quot;&gt;You’ve had some success using Quora for marketing. Can you describe how you’ve used it?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got started with Quora marketing a couple of years ago by accident. I happened to notice in my Google Analytics that I was getting a fair amount of traffic from Quora, and decided to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It turns out that someone had asked a question on Quora about finding a good feedback gathering solution, and someone else replied with a list of potential products. One of those was Doorbell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking around at other similar questions, I saw that most of the replies were people posting about their own product in a very obvious and self-promoting way. However there’s the Answer Wiki at the top of all the answers, which was usually empty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that it would be far more useful for people to get a list of tools right below the question instead of long paragraphs of self-promotion, I decided to start aggregating all the answers into the Wiki. And if Doorbell was a valid answer to the question, I’d include it in the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found this to be a good mix of new exposure for Doorbell, while adding value to people visiting the Quora thread. Much better than adding yet another long self-promoting reply to an already long Quora thread!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-do-you-think-about-competition&quot;&gt;How do you think about competition?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I generally try and ignore the competition. It would be all too easy to get caught up comparing your product to the competition, and then you’re constantly just trying to play catch-up on the feature-set you offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I instead try and focus on creating a good user experience for the users, while providing excellent support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a one-man team means I can’t compete on features with much bigger competitors. But I can definitely talk to my customers directly, and fix reported bugs in minutes instead of weeks. All of which provides a great experience for my customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-a-specific-lesson-youve-learned-from-running-doorbellio&quot;&gt;What’s a specific lesson you’ve learned from running Doorbell.io?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t underprice your product. Which may sound a bit like the “raise your prices” advice, but I see it a bit differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re starting your business, you might think that if the price is too high nobody will pay. But if the price is too low, how can I be confident as a customer that this is a sustainable business that won’t disappear on me overnight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you start thinking of the business in terms of something that needs to support you, and how many customers you’d need in order to do that, it might change your perspective a bit on how to price your product! Especially in SaaS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s something that I’ve seen myself with Doorbell as it has grown and I have needed to pay for more services. If something seems too cheap, I’d worry that it isn’t a sustainable business and I might not be able to rely on it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><category term="pricing" /><category term="competition" /><category term="growth" /><category term="query" /><summary type="html">Philip Manavopoulos is the founder of Doorbell.io, a tool for easily gathering in-app user feedback on all major platforms (web, iOS, and Android). Philip is from the United Kingdom, and has represented his country in sport competitions and played violin for almost 20 years.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Chad Brown from Orangedox</title><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/chad-brown-from-orangedox/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chad Brown from Orangedox" /><published>2018-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/chad-brown-from-orangedox</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/chad-brown-from-orangedox/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.linkedin.com/in/chadraymondbrown&quot;&gt;Chad Brown&lt;/a&gt; is CEO and Co-Founder of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.orangedox.com/&quot;&gt;Orangedox&lt;/a&gt;, which provides document tracking for Dropbox and Google Drive and is headquartered in Vancouver, Canada. Chad is an avid climber and hiker and has even visited Everest Base Camp in Nepal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;youve-pivoted-orangedox-a-couple-times-where-do-you-get-the-data-and-ideas-that-have-lead-you-to-make-the-decision-to-pivot&quot;&gt;You’ve pivoted Orangedox a couple times. Where do you get the data and ideas that have lead you to make the decision to pivot?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tend not to think of what we’ve done as pivots but rather as simply evolving the product. Typically, most of the ideas for changes to our product have come from direct feedback from our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, we’ve also done a variety of surveys with our customers. When customers leave the product we reach out to find out why. Usually, this is done as a personal email, as we’ve seen much higher response rates when doing it that way. Also we’ve run a “question of the week” survey on our weekly activity report that allows us to gauge what kind of future features are important to our customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;you-ran-a-service-based-company-before-this-what-made-you-want-to-switch-to-a-product-based-company&quot;&gt;You ran a service-based company before this. What made you want to switch to a product-based company?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the past 15 years I’ve run a service company that provides Business Intelligence consulting services. Around 5 years ago I decided I wanted to try building a product rather than just providing services. I think after 10 years of running the same type of business I felt like I needed a new challenge and coupled with the fact that I’m an engineer, I felt the push to build my own product rather than just consult on someone else’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-been-your-biggest-challenge-with-running-the-business-and-how-have-you-approached-solving-it&quot;&gt;What’s been your biggest challenge with running the business and how have you approached solving it?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest challenge has been trying to understand how to effectively market our product. With my service company everything was word of mouth so I never needed any real marketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a bootstrapped company we don’t have large budgets for marketing and we needed to find creative ways to get our product out there. This lead us to do things like crash the Dropbox user conference and hand out Lego mini-figures to get face time with their CEO Drew Houston, or spend countless hours answering online questions for people about how they can better leverage their documents in hopes that we can later win them over to our product.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><category term="product" /><category term="growth" /><category term="query" /><summary type="html">Chad Brown is CEO and Co-Founder of Orangedox, which provides document tracking for Dropbox and Google Drive and is headquartered in Vancouver, Canada. Chad is an avid climber and hiker and has even visited Everest Base Camp in Nepal.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">William Candillon from React Native Starter Kits</title><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/william-candillon-from-react-native-starter-kits/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="William Candillon from React Native Starter Kits" /><published>2018-04-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/william-candillon-from-react-native-starter-kits</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/william-candillon-from-react-native-starter-kits/">&lt;p&gt;William Candillon is a 31-year-old software engineer from France. He built &lt;a href=&quot;https://react-native.shop/&quot;&gt;React Native Starter Kits&lt;/a&gt; during a sabbatical and now has &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/wcandillon&quot;&gt;repos&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@wcandillon&quot;&gt;writing&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC806fwFWpiLQV5y-qifzHnA&quot;&gt;videos&lt;/a&gt; centered on React Native development. William currently lives in beautiful Zürich, Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;youre-big-into-transparency-what-are-the-benefits-of-being-transparent&quot;&gt;You’re big into transparency. What are the benefits of being transparent?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the case of the React Native Starter Kits, transparency as helped on two fronts. It enabled me to validate the product/market fit before investing a lot of work into the product. And once the product was ready, transparency has helped customers to get better insights about what they are buying, as well as better support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the get-go I shared my plans with the community. I built a landing page that contained screenshots of the finished product, even though not a single line of code was written yet. People could leave their email if they were interested in getting the kit once it was ready. This landing page was linked into my medium stories on React Native.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that, when the product picked up momentum, I started to code the starter kits live on YouTube. Not only has it been an enjoyable process, but the feedback from the community has been great, and it really gives potential customers a sense of what they would be buying. It has also helped tremendously with customer support. Many questions can be answered by pointing to the right YouTube video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-did-you-figure-out-who-your-target-market-is&quot;&gt;How did you figure out who your target market is?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A market place for React Native app already existed: &lt;a href=&quot;https://market.nativebase.io/&quot;&gt;NativeBase Market Place&lt;/a&gt;. This was extremely convenient because it takes time to build your own sales channel. Today, half of the sales are made directly, but it took many months to get to that result. So having an existing marketplace for the product was very valuable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The size of the React Native community is substantial, but there is a lot of mistrust in these starter kits, as there should be! 😅 Beginners in the community might not have enough knowledge to grasp the value provided by these kits, and people who are advanced enough to understand the value might consider doing it themselves, just because it’s fun to do. Therefore, the targeted segment in this large community is relatively small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-the-unique-challenges-and-advantages-youve-experienced-as-a-developer-who-is-trying-to-build-a-business&quot;&gt;What are the unique challenges and advantages you’ve experienced as a developer who is trying to build a business?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a developer, I’m focused on code quality, trying to reduce technical debt as much as possible, and delivering the best product possible. The downside of this love for good software engineering is that other aspects of the product like online marketing get neglected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developers always want to build cool things and continuously improve on them. But with the React Native Starter Kits, it is now clear to me that sometimes commercial data should drive the process instead.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><category term="transparency" /><category term="target market" /><category term="query" /><summary type="html">William Candillon is a 31-year-old software engineer from France. He built React Native Starter Kits during a sabbatical and now has repos, writing, and videos centered on React Native development. William currently lives in beautiful Zürich, Switzerland.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Arif Tukiman from RunCloud</title><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/arif-tukiman-from-runcloud/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Arif Tukiman from RunCloud" /><published>2018-04-18T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/arif-tukiman-from-runcloud</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/arif-tukiman-from-runcloud/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/arifcooll&quot;&gt;Arif Tukiman&lt;/a&gt; is CEO of Cool Code and back in January 2017, their team released &lt;a href=&quot;https://runcloud.io/&quot;&gt;RunCloud&lt;/a&gt;, which is a cloud server panel. It helps you set up, configure, manage, and monitor your VPSes on cloud hosting providers, and is specifically for PHP applications. Arif lives in Johor Bahru, Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-did-you-decide-to-drill-down-on-a-really-specific-niche-for-runcloud-and-what-have-been-the-benefits-of-doing-that&quot;&gt;Why did you decide to drill down on a really specific niche for RunCloud and what have been the benefits of doing that?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We built RunCloud to help our own web developers and the issues they faced during development, deployment, and maintenance. Based on their response, we saw the potential to productize the software — we just knew it could help other developers dealing with the same problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story really begins two years ago. My partner, Fikri, took the idea and thought that perhaps we could develop a tool for web hosting providers, but we didn’t have a ready and stable product at the time. We soon realized that the market was very competitive in that area with the presence of established players like WHM, CPanel, and Plesk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in early 2016, we pivoted our solution to cater more narrowly to PHP developers and freelance web designers. It’s a market closer to our hearts, given that we ourselves are PHP developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We validated the idea for this narrower product by taking a look at the market and checking out competitors. There were indeed competitors, but no major players like CPanel or Plesk. The businesses in our space were also just about 2-3 years in age at the time. And checking out their features, we believed we could offer the market something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My partners and I are computer science graduates. Amir and I were more into mobile app development. My other partner, Fikri, has more experience in security and web. Previously, Fikri had also created a VPN service that he’d sold subscriptions for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To build RunCloud as a business, I had to take on the role of CEO. Amir assumed the role of COO and led our marketing efforts, while Fikri, the brains behind the RunCloud architecture, became the CTO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we started working on the product, we were just college kids fresh out of our master’s degree. We had no work experience. So to be honest, money-wise, there was not a lot to spare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, we were also single college kids who didn’t require much to survive on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-the-challenges-associated-with-targeting-an-international-market-how-have-you-dealt-with-those-challenges&quot;&gt;What are the challenges associated with targeting an international market? How have you dealt with those challenges?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started charging from day one. We knew we had a good product by comparing ourselves to competitors who were charging way more for less features. Our packages are simple. A free account and a $10 per month account for an unlimited number of servers. That was the only way we knew we could make money then. (Of course, things have since changed.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use Braintree to charge our customers. This is the easiest solution for us, a Malaysian company, to be able to charge customers that come from all over the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, we’ve reached about 5,700 users from more than 25 countries worldwide. From current conversion to paid user, our MRR has been steadily growing at 24-29% from month to month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this is in line with a lesson we learned from legendary Jay Abraham when it comes to growing revenue. There are generally only three ways to go about it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More customers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bigger purchases per customer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More frequent purchases (from customers who come back)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a SaaS business, we’re already doing #3. And we are always working to acquire more customers, so that covers #1. And now, at last, we have #2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Backup Service, we are adding something else that customers can pay us for. To be honest, this wasn’t the original intention. We’d received a lot of feedback asking for a backup feature, so we implemented it. While we did have other plans and priorities a few months ago, we decided to listen to our customers’ needs instead. And I think that has already paid off very well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along those lines is a gem from &lt;a href=&quot;https://thefoundation.com/&quot;&gt;Dane Maxwell&lt;/a&gt; that I’d like to share: “In business, you will make a lot of mistakes and you will do alright if you do this one thing right — listen to your customers.” Great advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, when it comes to our own survival, RunCloud does not provide enough to cover our own wages yet. We still take in custom mobile and web application work. At times, we provide training related to programming. What we earn from RunCloud will most probably go back into the business. Earning in USD while living in Malaysia does help with living expenses, as they are low compared to USA or Europe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;whats-the-balance-between-building-for-customers-vs-competitors&quot;&gt;What’s the balance between building for customers vs competitors?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pay constant attention to your customers; don’t become so preoccupied with the activities of your competitors that you forget about your own business. Focus on improving your own business and ensuring that everyone who is associated with it has a great customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think Jeff Bezos said it best: “Obsess about customers, not competitors.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><category term="niches" /><category term="customers" /><category term="competition" /><category term="query" /><summary type="html">Arif Tukiman is CEO of Cool Code and back in January 2017, their team released RunCloud, which is a cloud server panel. It helps you set up, configure, manage, and monitor your VPSes on cloud hosting providers, and is specifically for PHP applications. Arif lives in Johor Bahru, Malaysia.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Manuel Frigerio from Maître</title><link href="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/manuel-frigerio-from-maitre/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manuel Frigerio from Maître" /><published>2018-04-10T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/manuel-frigerio-from-maitre</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.queryinterviews.com/interview/manuel-frigerio-from-maitre/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://manuel.friger.io/&quot;&gt;Manuel Frigerio&lt;/a&gt; is the founder of &lt;a href=&quot;https://maitreapp.co/&quot;&gt;Maître&lt;/a&gt;, which offers multiple tools for viral referral marketing. He is Italian, and lived in London for four years before doing the “digital nomad thing”™ for 8 months in south-east Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-have-been-your-pricing-decisions-for-maître-and-how-has-that-affected-the-overall-success-of-the-product&quot;&gt;What have been your pricing decisions for Maître and how has that affected the overall success of the product?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve changed my mind about pricing 100 times. In the beginning, I went for a one-off fee simply because I couldn’t be bothered building a subscription system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Financially, it was a big mistake. People were getting far more value out of the product than what I was charging for. In short, I was leaving money on the table. Being priced so low had the obvious advantage of being very attractive for startups, which helped in the early days, but ultimately we didn’t want to be the cheapest on the market but the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, we have increased the pricing 5 times and moved to a subscription model. That move has meant first of all the financial survival of the company and expanding the team to support our ever-growing number of customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-your-thoughts-on-paid-advertising-for-early-startups&quot;&gt;What are your thoughts on paid advertising for early startups?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just avoid it. It’s simply not worth the hassle. Like many startups, we tried paid ads and like almost everyone we gave up after wasting a few hundred dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem with paid ads for early startups is that very few people actually know how to set up a decent campaign. And without that knowledge, you’re very likely to waste money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And regardless of your knowledge, early startups should focus on recruiting users one-by-one, do “things that don’t scale”. Paid ads might be a strategy that works once you reach product/market fit and you need to scale but in the early days is, at most, laziness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;maître-is-one-of-the-most-upvoted-products-on-product-hunt-can-you-give-us-a-piece-of-advice-for-launching-on-ph-and-tell-us-how-much-of-the-success-there-depends-on-luck&quot;&gt;Maître is one of the most-upvoted products on Product Hunt. Can you give us a piece of advice for launching on PH, and tell us how much of the success there depends on luck?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product Hunt has changed a lot since we launch on it. Ryan and the PH team have executed incredibly well. That said, I think there is timeless advice when launching on PH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, be nice. No seriously. Product Hunt is a community, but some people use it as a disposable piece of software. Don’t be that person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember that Product Hunt is not the right place to launch anything. It’s undeniable that the PH community loves some things (crypto, kittens, the 3,285,434th colour palette app) more than others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preparation is important. Don’t just on PH, plan it carefully. It’s incredible the difference it will make. I’ve actually written a &lt;a href=&quot;https://manuel.friger.io/blog/product-hunt&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; about our launch. Some information is out of date, but most of it is still relevant.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;queryinterviews&quot;}</name></author><category term="pricing" /><category term="paid advertising" /><category term="query" /><summary type="html">Manuel Frigerio is the founder of Maître, which offers multiple tools for viral referral marketing. He is Italian, and lived in London for four years before doing the “digital nomad thing”™ for 8 months in south-east Asia.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://www.queryinterviews.com/img/query-logo.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>